She was the only man he ever loved.
Soldier's Girl is a tv movie, drama, romance film directed by Frank Pierson.
This true story, which takes place in Fort Campbell, KY, tells the
heart-wrenching story of the life and tragic death of soldier Barry Winchell.
His love for Calpernia Addams, a transgender nightclub performer, was
misunderstood by his fellow soldiers and eventually led to his murder.
Barry Winchell, played by Troy Garity.
Calpernia Addams / Scottie, played by Lee Pace.
Sergeant Carlos Diaz, played by Andre Braugher.
Justin Fisher, played by Shawn Hatosy.
Calvin Glover, played by Philip Eddolls.
Henry Millens, played by Merwin Mondesir.
Soldier's Girl is a 2003 biographical drama television film
written by Ron Nyswaner and directed by Frank Pierson.
It is based on the true story of the relationship between Calpernia Addams and Barry Winchell and the events that led
up to Winchell's murder by fellow soldiers Justin Fisher and Calvin Glover on the 4th of July 1999.
The film stars Troy Garity as Winchell and Lee Pace as Addams.
The film premiered on Showtime on May 31, 2003.
Soldier's Girl was listed among the ten best Television Programs
of the Year (2003) by the American Film Institute.
The film explores themes of kentucky, based on
true story, murder, soldier, lgbt.
The tone is emotional.